(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Puppy, fuzzy, happy, sisters!
Fuwawa Abyssgard!
Mococo Abyssgard!
Are you ready?
行くぞー！
Let's go!
BAU BAU! BAU BAU!
FUWAMOCO Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival!
BAU BAU!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be together with you.
Lifetime, showtime, anytime, BAU BAU!
Yeah! Future is bright.
Fluffy fuzzy yappi sisters!
Lifetime showtime!
FUWA! MOCO! FUWA! MOCO!
FUWA! MOCO! BAU BAU BAU BAU!
My heart n' soul n' tail are FUWAWA
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe
FUWA! MOCO! BAU BAU!
I love being tricky, doggy kisses are for me
I love lots of walkies, don't need no leashes for me
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere
FUWAMOCO together, take us along with you
Barking oh so merrily!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be together with you.
Lifetime, showtime, anytime, BAU BAU!
一生涯 sing with you
For a lifetime, sing with you
Stars wink, moon spotlight, furr-ever glow
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be together with you.
Lifetime, showtime, anytime, BAU BAU!
Yeah! Future is bright.
Fluffy fuzzy yappi sisters!
BAU! WOOOO! BAU! WOOOO!
Way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell
Holding back, doggy dog kept sealed away
Bouta burst, fluff n' fuzz, we're meant to be free
Bouta burst, fluff & fuzz,
we're meant to be free
Dreams sparklin' within our eyes
Gonna keep you smilin',
but my sneakers won't stop flyin' by
Even though we're still just a pair
of scaredy puppy dogs
The bond that we share as twins
is irreplaceable
We're a pair unbreakable!
And that's why
いつだって
always,
It's that day!
Today!
Lifetime!
Showtime!
Not tomorrow!
BAU BAU!
一生涯
For a lifetime,
Walk with you!
Good times,
bad times,
it doesn't matter!
いつだって
Always,
It's that day!
Lifetime!
Showtime!
Everyday!
BAU BAU!
Yeah,
二人は
The two of us are
Happy lucky puppy sisters!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU!
Everybody BAU BAU!
Hallo hallo BAU BAU!
ダメダメ ノンノン！
No no, non non!
Don't touch the ears!
モフモフ ノンノン！
Fluff fluff, non non!
Don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ！
I'm not a chihuahua!
フワワだよ！BAU！
I'm Fuwawa! BAU!
フワワじゃないよ！
I'm not Fuwawa!
モココだよ！BAU！
I'm Mococo! BAU!
Twin demon guard dog
sisters, yeah BAU!
And together we're...
FUWAMOCO!
Gather up our dreams
And suddenly you'll come to realize
There's as many as there are stars
Illuminating the night sky
Never-ending dreams
We don't know if they all can be achieved
But we'll keep on going furr-ever
Together here with you!
It's showtime
一緒にいたい
I want to be with you
It's showtime
一緒にいたい
I want to be with you
It's showtime
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you!
Fuwa fuwa
Moco moco
Hand in hand with you
Bring your smile
rain or shine
We'll protect it
won't forget our
Pledge to you!
It's showtime
一緒にいたい
I want to be with you
Lifetime
Showtime
anytime BAU BAU!
一生涯
For a lifetime,
Sing with you
Stars wink
Moon spotlight
Furr-ever glow!
It's showtime
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you!
Lifetime
Showtime
anytime BAU BAU!
And
together we're
Happy fuzzy yuppy sisters!
Let's hear you!
Say BAU BAU!
FUWA!
MOCO!
Yeah!
FUWA!
MOCO!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU!
BAU BAU!
Welcome to our...
FUWAMOCO Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival!
BAU BAU!
Thank you so much for coming to celebrate
our birthday with us!
始まりました！
It has begun!
BAU BAU!
今日は生誕ライブに来てくれて
Thank you for coming to our
ありがとう！
birthday live today!
Thank you!
Well, to continue off from yesterday's variety show
shenanigans...
Today we have a big concert!
Yeah!
And can you believe it?
It's already been three years!
Right?
Our third birthday in Hololive too!
Thank you!
But Mococo-chan,
we can't forget that really important thing though!
Hai!
Yes!
Introductions!
Ah, yeah!
Okay!
I'm not a chihuahua!
I'm Fuwawa!
I'm not Fuwawa!
I'm Mococo!
We are Hololive English Advent's
twin demon guard dog sisters!
Together we are...
FUWAMOCO!
BAU BAU!
And look!
We have an amazing birthday festival stage here!
Amazing stage!
It's so big!
So spacious!
And it's such a big blue sky too!
Fuwawa!
Call it!
Okay, here we go!
Three, two, one...
BAU BAU!
It's so big and wide!
Wide!
Thank you, Ruffians, for being here today!
But singing and dancing today
is not just going to be us, right?
No!
We're also here with some very special guests too!
そう！今日はとっても素敵なゲストさんも
Yes! Today we have some wonderful guests
来てるから
here with us,
ステージを楽しみにしててくださいね！
so please look forward to the stage!
Yeah!
そして
And also,
もう一人...
one more person...
謎のゲストさんも...
a mystery guest as well...
誰かな？
Who could it be?
BAU BAU!
But a birthday wouldn't be complete without this, right?
Right!
Something very important!
I think you know what!
But...
Hashtag!
Yes!
The birthday hashtag!
Right up here
you can see our birthday hashtag!
#FWMCbday26
That it is!
Please, please post your thoughts!
Take lots of photos!
Screenshots!
ぜひハッシュタグで感想呟いてください！
Please tweet your thoughts using the hashtag!
写真もね！
Photos too!
後でポチしに行くからね！
We'll go like them later!
BAU BAU!
We'll go check all your thoughts
after the show!
So...
BAU BAU!
Right after this, so don't miss it, okay?
Yeah!
最後には名言のアンコールライブもありますので、ぜひ見に来てくださいね！
There will be a 'Famous Quotes' encore live at the very end, so please come watch!
Bau bau!
Wow!
You know, the concert is halfway, right?
So we get singing a little bit more?
Yeah!
For this next song...
I think we need a special guest with us, right?
Yeah!
Okay, let's call her on together.
Okay!
Calli-senpai!
Hey hey hey hey hey hey hey!
Ah! 皆さん！
Ah! Everyone!
Bau bau!
Today only, I am also a dog.
Shinigami dog.
Yeah!
Thank you for coming to our birthday!
Thank you for inviting me! I'm happy to be here!
What's up, Ruffians?
But I see you have a pretty nice shirt there, huh?
I do. Wow, look at this logo.
What could it say?
Check it out. Respect.
With respect.
But you know, it might be cute if we matched, right?
Right!
Ah, well... maybe we'll just go run...
...and we'll get changed.
Entertain them with the 'Bau Bau's for a second.
Okay, I got this.
No problem.
They won't bite... maybe.
Yeah, okay.
Bau bau!
Ruffians!
Welcome to Mori Calliope's super special splits challenge segment!
行くぞ！
Here we go!
できないかも… できない！
I might not be able to... I can't!
I can't... I'm sorry, I can't.
I can't do it!
I did my best.
Did we change?
We changed, right?
Yes! See?
I can't even bend.
But now... we're matching!
Matching!
Twinning!
Tripleting?
Tripleting!
Ah, that has a nice ring to it.
And this next song...
is one that FUWAMOCO...
We wanted to sing with you for such a long time!
Yes!
Something nostalgic... and I think you'll be able to see why.
There's some rap... as well.
But it's also very cute, right?
次歌う曲は、Calli先輩と一緒にずっと歌いたかった大好きな曲ですね！
This next song is one we've wanted to sing with Calli-senpai for a long time; it's our favorite!
そうですね！
That's right!
It's both cute... it's cool...
But, I think, you know, it shares an important part that...
You know, you should be proud of what you like, right?
Important meaning of being proud... being strong about what you like, yeah!
Yeah, your likes!
You know, whether that be games...
Or anime...
Or idols!
Figures!
Or maybe even... VTubers?
Yeah!
You know, after all, life is more fun when...
...you're just true to yourself.
Right?
Definitely. I agree.
So, are you ready to sing this song for you?
Okay!
Let's do the title call together, okay?
Yes!
聴いてください！
Please listen!
Like! Like! Like!
Comic, I like it!
Music, I like it!
Game, I like it!
Animation, I like it!
Figure, I like it!
Movie, I like it!
Wonder, I like it!
Hobby, I like it!
Go go go go go go go go!
Do you like it? I like it!
人生楽しんだもん勝ちの裏技
The cheat code to life is that the one who enjoys it wins.
好きなもの好きって言えたらそれ Supernova
If you can say you like what you like, that's a Supernova.
快感中枢即MAX脳内麻薬
Pleasure center instantly MAX, brain narcotics.
まるでできたかき鳴らし勝手に歌うバンドマン
Like a bandman strumming and singing as they please.
Classic Magic 魔力毒で局面きっと軸は一緒でしょ
Classic Magic, with magic poison, the phase and axis are surely the same.
No reason キラめき無双
No reason, sparkling peerless.
今すぐ Let's mix down!
Right now, Let's mix down!
君が部屋にいたってリンクすれば Concert
Even if you're in your room, if we link, it's a concert.
いつだって Only lonely only lonely just your universe say joy
Always only lonely only lonely just your universe say joy
I like it! Like it!
スキになれば
If you fall in love with it...
きっと全てがカラフルで
...surely everything will be colorful.
Lucky! Lucky!
星屑さえ光る宝物さ
Even stardust becomes a shining treasure.
Yeah yeah yeah!
I like it! Like it!
キミに会えた
I was able to meet you.
やっと今日からヨロシクね
Finally, nice to meet you starting today.
ホラ キラキラ 夢みたい
Look, sparkling, it's like a dream.
早く抱きしめたい
I want to hug you soon.
アレもコレも欲しくて
I want this and that.
神様に祈ってる
I'm praying to God.
次は　何に　しようかな
I wonder what I should do next.
アレばっか悪くない　特マルは
That's not bad, I'll give it a special pass,
よっとばす　サイン　言葉 Like It Like It
Sending a sign, words say 'Like It Like It'.
360度パノラマ
360-degree panorama,
全方向大好きの陣
a formation of loving everything in all directions.
何が一等でもいいから
Whatever is first prize, it's fine,
飲み込める自分のアイテム
I can swallow it, my own item.
Like a superstar fireman
無敵 Candy 他大体ライセイ
invincible Candy, everything else is for the next life.
望んでる彼もきっと
Even he who wishes for it will surely
現世が愛しくなるはずなのさ
come to love this present life.
なろうとしてなるもんじゃない
It's not something you try to become,
人生楽しんで歩こうじゃない
let's walk through life enjoying it, shall we?
自分に素直であれ
Be true to yourself,
Spotlight 僕らを照らせ
Spotlight, shine on us.
今日も愛を叫ぶだけだ
Today too, I just shout love.
そうじゃない Song for you
Isn't that right? Song for you.
I Like It Like It
手を伸ばせば
if you reach out your hand,
きっと全てがミラクルで
surely everything will be a miracle.
Happy Happy
日常でさえ
even everyday life
夢の物語さ
is a dream story.
I Like It Like It
キミに会えた
I met you,
ずっと離さないでいてね
please never let me go.
ホラ　キラキラ
Look, sparkling
虹みたい
like a rainbow,
世界はまわりだす
the world starts to turn.
Water gun, go, go, go!
BAU BAU BAU!
スキでスキでスキで
I love it, I love it, I love it,
勝負台から手に入れたい
I want to get it from the platform,
この感情ハドメと財布と
this emotion, brakes, and wallet,
真剣勝負
a serious match.
ためらわないのがいいでしょ？
It's good not to hesitate, right?
そう！
Yes!
恋ももっと事件
Love is also more of an incident.
でもそれが僕の等身大
But that is my true self.
ダッシュでズバっと世界を確認
Dash and zip, confirm the world,
いわゆるひとつの模様相
a so-called single pattern phase.
素直になれたなら Happy Days
If I could be honest, Happy Days.
I Like It Like It
好きになれば
if you fall in love,
きっと全てがカラフルで
surely everything will be colorful.
Lucky Lucky
星屑さえ
even stardust
光る宝物さ
is a shining treasure.
I Like It Like It
キミに会えた
I met you,
やっと今日からヨロシクね
finally, nice to meet you starting today.
ホラ　キラキラ
Look, sparkling
夢みたい
like a dream,
早く抱きしめたい
I want to hug you soon.
I Like It Like It
手を伸ばせば
if you reach out your hand,
きっと全てがミラクルで
surely everything will be a miracle.
Happy Happy
日常でさえ
even everyday life
夢の物語さ
is a dream story.
I Like It Like It
キミに会えた
I met you,
ずっと離さないでいてね
please never let me go.
ホラ　キラキラ
Look, sparkling
虹みたい
like a rainbow,
世界はまわりだす
the world starts to turn.
かわいい！絶対！
Cute! Definitely!
I like FUWAMOCO!
BAU BAU!
Please listen to our next song.
Je t'aime, Je t'aime.
街角に並ぶ
Lined up on the street corner,
映画のポスター
the movie posters.
もうこの街にも
Even in this town,
秋は来た
autumn has already come.
渋滞の向こうに
Beyond the traffic jam,
ため息を返す
I return a sigh.
キャンセルしないで
Don't cancel.
Mon amour pour toi
My love for you,
ハートのロケットに
in the heart locket,
隠した写真誰も知らない
no one knows the hidden photo.
本気の恋
Serious love,
神様は気づいてる
God has noticed it.
Je t'aime Je t'aime
I love you, I love you
叶わない夢なんて見たくないわ
I don't want to dream dreams that won't come true.
でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
But romance is awakening.
愛してるわ
I love you.
クレープに描く
Drawn on a crepe,
愛の傘の下で
under the umbrella of love.
止まぬ雨の音
The sound of rain that won't stop,
Je t'aime Je t'aime
I love you, I love you.
こんな夜に
On a night like this,
したくはないから
I don't want to fight,
ほんの5分でも
Even for just five minutes,
会いたい
I want to see you.
キャンディ・ショップも
Candy shops too,
猫のショップも
Cat shops too,
あなたがいないと
Without you,
つまらない
It's boring.
ジャケットのポケットに
In the jacket pocket,
入れたままのコインに
On the coin left inside,
賭けるわ
I'll bet,
恋の行方
The outcome of this love.
神様が知っている
Only God knows.
Je t'aime Je t'aime
I love you, I love you.
退屈な恋なんて
A boring love...
したくないわ
...is not what I want.
あっという間に溺れてく
Drowning in the blink of an eye.
“今がすべて”
"Now is everything."
カフェ・オ・レが冷めて
The cafe au lait gets cold,
しまうその前に
Before that happens,
もいちどKISSして
Kiss me once more.
Je t'aime Je t'aime
I love you, I love you.
物語に鍵をかけて
Lock up the story.
Toujours un jour
Always, one day.
あなたのことばかりを
Only about you...
夢見ている
...I am dreaming.
Mon amour
My love.
Je t'aime Je t'aime
I love you, I love you.
叶わない夢なんて
A dream that won't come true...
見たくないわ
...is not what I want to see.
でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
But romance is awakening.
“愛してるわ”
"I love you."
クレープに描く
Drawing on a crepe,
愛の傘の下で
Under the umbrella of love.
止まぬ雨の音
The sound of rain that won't stop.
Je t'aime Je t'aime
I love you, I love you.
Mon amour, pour toi
My love, for you.
退屈な恋なんて
A boring love...
したくないわ
...is not what I want.
あっという間に溺れてく
Drowning in the blink of an eye.
“今がすべて”
"Now is everything."
カフェ・オ・レが冷めて
The cafe au lait gets cold,
しまうその前に
Before that happens,
もいちどKISSして
Kiss me once more.
Je t'aime Je t'aime
I love you, I love you.
Wow! Bau! Doki tte sashita?
Wow! Bau! Did your heart skip a beat?
Oh, it's setting already, huh?
Perfect timing!
Well, that last song was...
Je t'aime Je t'aime!
What did you think?
Just a little bit more nostalgic?
Yeah, maybe even a bit melancholic almost?
You know, some city pop vibes too.
The choreography is cute too, right?
We hope it made you feel nice and warm and fluffy fluffy inside.
Well, you know, with the sun setting now...
It's starting to feel a bit... romantic almost, right?
Well, I guess it's the perfect time to call up our next guest!
Yeah!
Here we go!
AZKi-senpai! AkiRose-senpai!
FUWAMOCOちゃん！
Fuwamoco-chan!
Happy Birthday!
嬉しいバウバウ！
We're happy bau bau!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
自己紹介お願いします！
Please introduce yourselves!
こ、こ、こ、こあずき！AZKiです！
Ko-ko-ko-koazuki! I'm AZKi!
アローナ！異世界のヨシュハーフエルフ、アキロゼことアキ・ローゼンタールです！
Aloona! A half-elf from another world, Aki Rosenthal, also known as AkiRose!
わぁー！来てくれてありがとう！
Wow! Thank you for coming!
衣装も... ステージも... すごいね！
The outfits... and the stage... are amazing!
AZKi先輩とアキロゼ先輩の歌声がすごく大好きなので...
We really love AZKi-senpai and AkiRose-senpai's singing voices, so...
一緒に... 歌えたら嬉しいなって曲があって...
There's a song we thought we'd be happy to sing together...
お姉さんたちなので
Since we are the 'big sisters' here...
あら？ そうですか？
Oh? Is that so?
ちょっとこの曲で行こうかなと思いました
I thought we might go with this song.
なるほど！
I see!
ちょっと日も暮れてますし...
The sun is starting to set a bit, too...
ちょっとロマンチックになりましたね
It's become a bit romantic, hasn't it?
実はちょっぴりセクシーかも？
Actually, it might be a little sexy?
セクシーかも？
Sexy?
セクシーな曲？
A sexy song?
お願いしたことがあるんですけど...
There's actually something I wanted to request...
何ですか？
What is it?
アキロゼ先輩...
AkiRose-senpai...
えっと この曲を歌う前に少し あの...
Um, before singing this song, just a little, um...
セクシーなウォームアップ...
A sexy warm-up...
セクシーウォームアップ？！
Sexy warm-up?!
してもいいですか？
Is it okay if we do it?
OK！ やる！
OK! Let's do it!
じゃあまずセクシーだ
Alright, first, the sexy part.
体を作るために...
To prepare our bodies...
自分のボディを撫でて
Stroke your own body.
撫でて？
Stroke?
撫でて...
Stroke it...
頭撫でて...
Stroke your head...
足から...
From your legs...
上に...
Moving upwards...
不思議！
How mysterious!
撫でて撫でて
Stroke, stroke.
やってみて
Try doing it.
恥ずかしい！
It's embarrassing!
撫でて... 全部みたいな
Stroke... like everything.
モコちゃん いいよ！
Moco-chan, that's good!
可愛いよ！
You're cute!
撫でるがセクシーだから...
Because stroking is sexy...
もう一回 もう一回
One more time, one more time.
AZKiちゃん なんかさ セクシーだけど可愛い
AZKi-chan, you're like, sexy but cute.
やった！ いいですか？
Yay! Is it okay?
やっぱこうやって...
You gotta do it like this...
Oh, nice!
あら あら
My, my.
あと しっぽ しっぽ
Also, the tail, the tail.
しっぽ？
Tail?
しっぽフリフリも
Wag the tail, too.
モコちゃん しっぽフリフリ
Moco-chan, wag your tail.
フリフリフリフリ...
Wag, wag, wag, wag...
OK, OK. いいんじゃない？
OK, OK. Isn't that good?
いいよ いいよ
It's good, it's good.
ウォームアップできたよ
Warm-up complete.
じゃあ いい感じになりましたね
Well then, the vibe has become quite nice.
次の曲いきましょうか
Shall we move on to the next song?
じゃあ 聴いてください
Then, please listen.
DISCOTHEQUE!
CHU-RU CHU-RU CHU-RU PA-YA-PA
DISCO LADY DISCO LADY
DEEP EMOTION DEEP EMOTION
SWEETIE DARLIN' 踊りましょう
SWEETIE DARLIN' let's dance
弾ける BEAUTY LADY
Bursting with energy, BEAUTY LADY
生まれ変わって 甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
そっと
Softly
彩りたいの
I want to color it
グズグズするな 唇
Don't hesitate, lips
ピンク色の艶めくネイル
Pink glossy nails
ガラスの向こう側に映る素顔 シュールなDays
The real face reflected in the glass, surreal Days
人気だけを競うなんて痛い
Competing only for popularity is painful
心の中 ソフトにKnock
Knock softly on the heart
そばにいてほしいよ
I want you by my side
月のミラーボール
The moon's mirror ball
照らされて
Illuminating us
MY DARLIN' ねぇ VIVIDな恋しましょ
MY DARLIN' hey, let's have a VIVID love
弾ける SEXY BEAUTY
Bursting SEXY BEAUTY
生まれ変わって 甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
そっと彩る MY LOVE FOR YOU
Softly coloring, MY LOVE FOR YOU
世界は変わる
The world changes
CHU-RU CHU-RU CHU-RU PA-YA-PA
DRAMATICな情熱
DRAMATIC passion
恐れない 大丈夫
Don't be afraid, it's okay
見つめ続けたくて
I want to keep watching you
COLORFULな SWEET STORY
COLORFUL and SWEET STORY
心深く刻み込む
Carving it deep into my heart
小さな悩みが訪れても
Even if small worries visit us
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
If you chant the spell of love
そう きっと 果てない空
Yes, surely, from the endless sky
星屑のシャワーが降り注ぐ
A shower of stardust will rain down
だから HAPPY STATION 目指してゆこう
So let's aim for the HAPPY STATION
FIFTY FIFTY 合わせて
Combining FIFTY-FIFTY
100%以上の愛
To make a love over 100%
揺るぎない ここにあると
Unwavering, right here
私 思ってる
I truly believe
CHU-RU CHU-RU CHU-RU PA-YA-PA
裏腹な仕草
Contradictory gestures,
交錯する自分
my conflicted self.
君にありのまま
I want you to love me
好きでいてほしいと
just as I am.
願いは
My wish is
(Reflection)
素敵な
a wonderful
(Illusion)
My darling もっと一緒に踊りましょう
My darling, let's dance together more.
Secret night 素敵な
Secret night, a wonderful...
Love is so true なのでこれ以上
Love is so true, so any more than this,
二人のハートで愛
with our two hearts, love...
奏で合わせて
...play in harmony.
My darling ねえビビッドな恋しましょ
My darling, hey, let's have a vivid love.
弾ける Sexy Beauty
Bursting Sexy Beauty.
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn, a sweet dream.
そっと彩る My Love ほら
Softly coloring My Love, look.
世界は変わる
The world changes.
チュール チュール チュール パヤパ
Chu-ru chu-ru chu-ru pa-ya-pa
燃え尽きるわ
I'll burn out,
この恋多分
this love, probably.
どんな終幕が来ようと
No matter what ending comes,
覚悟してる
I'm prepared.
余裕なんて
Composure...
ほとんどない
...I have almost none.
必死でしがみついてるだけ
I'm just desperately clinging on.
あなたの目
Your eyes,
優しく抱き寄せる腕
the arms that gently pull me close.
全てが
Everything,
(全てが)
(everything)
初めての
is my first...
Fall in love だとは
...fall in love.
Kiss me
離さないで
don't let go.
Kiss me
自然なままで
stay natural.
この不安も
This anxiety too,
拭い取ってねえ
wipe it away, hey.
(ねえ ねえ ねえ...)
(Hey hey hey...)
Touch me
その指先
those fingertips.
Touch me
その眼差しで
with that gaze.
この私を
Wrap this me...
包み込んで Please
...up, Please.
(Please please please...)
愛してる
I love you.
蘇るわ
It comes back to me,
昨日のこと
yesterday's events.
あんなに心が揺れたの
My heart wavered that much,
初めてだもん
it's the first time.
寂しすぎて
Too lonely,
時に怖い
sometimes scary.
二人でいられないこの
This time when we can't be together...
時が Ah
...Ah.
雨の朝
A rainy morning,
暖かな部屋でコーヒー
coffee in a warm room.
大人の
An adult's...
フリから
...pretense turns into...
本当の大人になりそう
...becoming a real adult.
Kiss me
危険なほど
enough to be dangerous.
Kiss me
甘い口づけ
a sweet kiss.
今日の願いを
Today's wish...
全部叶えてねえ
...grant it all, hey.
(ねえ ねえ ねえ...)
(Hey hey hey...)
Knock me
その魂で
with that soul.
Knock me
窓を叩いて
knock on the window.
こんな私を
Make this me...
安心させて Please
...feel safe, Please.
(Please please please...)
愛してる
I love you.
Kiss me
いけないほど
A dangerous amount.
Kiss me
甘いくちづけ
A sweet kiss.
こんな願いを
All these wishes,
全部叶えてね
Grant them all, okay?
Please...
Lock me
その魂で
With that soul.
Knock me
窓を叩いて
Knock on the window.
今度私を
This time,
安心させて Please
Reassure me, please.
Please...
愛してる
I love you.
Ruffians! Are you ready?
Let's kill you!
Please enjoy!
Triangle Dreamer!
Day by day
日に日に募るの乙女心
A maiden's heart grows stronger day by day.
同じクラス斜め前の
In the same class, diagonally in front,
正しい人
Is the righteous person.
カッコよくはない
He's not exactly cool,
だけど優しい
But he is kind.
いつも頼れる彼
He's someone I can always rely on.
何だって話せる
I can talk to her about anything,
親友の女の子
My best girl friend.
スポーツ万能
Good at sports,
勉強もできて
And good at studying too,
女子力マックスです
Her girl power is maxed out.
どこにでもある
It can be found anywhere,
よくあること
It's a common thing.
急に彼女が
Suddenly she says,
あのね 実は私 好きな人がいるのって
"Hey, actually, there's someone I like."
ちょマジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形
Triangle,
三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangular love is whimsical.
一瞬で
In an instant,
一瞬で崩れるバランス
The balance collapses in an instant.
ベタなマンガ
Like a cliché manga,
みたいなフラグ
It's a flag.
まさかね
No way...
自分が立てちゃうなんて
That I'd raise it myself,
残念すぎます
It's just too unfortunate.
三角形
Triangle,
三角形の恋は不安定
Triangular love is unstable.
なんちゃって
Just kidding,
なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
This category can't be dismissed as 'just kidding'.
恋と友情 ゆらゆらめいて
Love and friendship flickering waveringly.
なんか青春しちゃいます
I'm kinda living my youth.
わたし困っちゃいます
I'm really troubled.
完敗です
It's a complete defeat.
お似合いすぎるわ
They match too well,
勝てっこない
I can't possibly win.
悔しいけどとか
"I'm frustrated" or something,
そんなんじゃなくて本心
It's not that, it's my true feeling.
ていうか既に応援モード
Actually, I'm already in cheering mode.
むしろ清々しい
It's rather refreshing.
だけど彼女は不思議な顔
But she has a strange look on her face.
真剣な目で
With serious eyes,
そうじゃなくて 私 あなたが好き ごめんって
She said, "It's not that, I like you. Sorry."
ちょマジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形
Triangle,
三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangular love is whimsical.
一瞬で
In an instant,
一瞬で崩れるバランス
The balance collapses in an instant.
わたし あなた
Me, you...
彼女とわたし
Her and me...
超絶複雑 百合展開は
Super complex yuri development is...
想定外です
Totally unexpected!
三角形
Triangle,
三角形の恋は不安定
Triangular love is unstable.
なんちゃって
Just kidding,
なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
This category can't be dismissed as 'just kidding'.
解けないパズル
This unsolvable puzzle,
与え給うた神よ
Oh God who bestowed it upon me,
恨んじゃいます
I resent you.
悩んじゃいます
I'm worried.
あーもうすごいヤバイ！
Ah, this is really bad!
好きだよ… 好きだけど…
I love you... I love you, but...
ってそういう意味じゃなくて
Not in that way...
だって女の子同士だし
Because we're both girls...
ねえ神様 どうしたらいいの？
Hey God, what should I do?
私 どうしたいの？
What do I want to do?
ヘルプミー！
Help me!
なんか変だ 愛に国境も歳も性別も関係ない
Something's strange. Love has no borders, age, or gender.
けど けど けど
But, but, but...
三角形 三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, triangle love is whimsical.
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
Balance that collapses in an instant.
普通の恋 夢見てたのに
Even though I dreamed of a normal love.
ノーマル設定の私じゃちょっと無理ゲーすぎます
For me with normal settings, it's a bit too much of an impossible game.
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangle love is unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
A category where 'just kidding' isn't enough.
彼女のこと 好きになれたらなんて妄想しちゃいます
I end up having delusions like 'if only I could like her'.
私 どうかしてます
Something is wrong with me.
行くよー！
Let's go!
Thank you!
Thank you Ruffians!
That was so much fun!
I got a bit dizzy though...
With the bubbles changing so quickly!
Nice and fast!
Those last two songs we sung were...
'Kiss Me Aishiteru' and 'Triangle Dreamer'!
Reference to Fubuki-senpai, Mio-senpai, and Subaru-senpai!
We have a tiny, tiny announcement!
It's our birthday right?
It's time to celebrate both of our birthdays with our FuwaMoco 2024 Birthday Merch!
First, the Fuwa Fuwa Idol Fuwawa and Moco Moco Idol Mococo Acrylic Stands.
Illustrated by Icomochi-mama!
They're rather big compared to regular acrylic stands.
Next, the Ehehe Angel and Hoeh?! Devil Rubber Figurines.
We're now palm-sized figures perfect for displaying on your desk.
This one is big!
We finally have FuwaMoco plushies in our out-and-about casual outfits.
It's the Yappy Puppy FuwaMoco Sounds Plushies!
But this time, we also speak when you hug us!
おしゃべりパピーMOCOCOぬいぐるみ
Talking Puppy MOCOCO Plushie
ふわもこだよ！
It's Fuwamoco!
ぎゅっとすると、色々喋るよ！
Squeeze it, and it says all kinds of things!
どんなボイスが出るか、お楽しみに！
Look forward to what voices will pop out!
We have the FWMC GO Finger Puppets!
They both come with one extra Ruffian kigurumi costume you can dress us up in and bring around with you everywhere!
FUWAMOCOの指パペット！
FWMC Finger Puppets!
どこでも一緒に連れて行けるサイズで、着せ替えラフィアンズ衣装もあるよ！
They're a size you can take anywhere, and they come with a Ruffian costume change!
Finally, we have two different ASMR Voice Packs!
"Back from a Fluffy Date with Fuwawa" and...
..."Sweet and Fuzzy Needy Puppy from Mococo"!
ASMRボイスは、英語と日本語、両方で収録してます！
The ASMR voices are recorded in both English and Japanese!
They made our hearts beat so fast...
Be ready to blush when you take a listen to them!
The merch is separated into two sets...
Fuwawa's Birthday Merch, and Mococo's Birthday Merch!
If you purchase the full set, they come with bonuses...
...including a cheki-style card with a special bonus voice!
グッズはFUWAWAセットとMOCOCOセットに分かれています！
The merch is divided into a FUWAWA set and a MOCOCO set!
セットごとにチェキ風カードと特典ボイスが付きます！
Each set comes with a cheki-style card and a bonus voice!
The regular version will have a foil-stamped replica signature and message, so it will be just as cute!
数量限定セットは直筆サイン付きだよ！
The limited quantity set comes with a handwritten autograph!
We put lots of love into each and every signature...
...so we hope you look forward to it!
たくさんの愛情を込めてサイン書きますね！
We'll put lots of love into writing the signatures!
Please check out the Hololive Official Online Shop and look for the link in the description or comment area, okay?
ぜひ、ホロライブ公式ショップにてチェックしてください！
Please check it out at the official Hololive shop!
Bye bye!
What did you think?
Our birthday merch is pretty cute, huh?
The reservations are going on sale right after the birthday live here ends...
...so don't forget, okay?
生誕のグッズの予約は、このあと開始しますので...
Reservations for the birthday merch will start right after this...
...お忘れずにチェックしてくださいね！
...so please don't forget to check it out!
You can go to the link below or on the side here!
Don't forget, okay?
We put a lot of love into it and Ikomochi-mama too!
Thank you, Ikomochi-mama!
Right after this ends... Time to go go go!
Well, we performed lots of special collab songs with our dear senpai...
...but there's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet, right?
そう、まだ会ってない謎のゲストが一人いるんだよ！
That's right, there's one mystery guest we haven't met yet!
Well, should we give the Ruffians a hint first?
Ruffians, you're curious right?
Who could it be?
YAGOO-san?
That's a good guess maybe...
Maybe you should get ready...
...because, you know, they aren't quite as bad as Pero...
...but they can get pretty nasty sometimes!
Moco-chan, you're not going to be rude to our next guest or anything... right?
Especially before calling them out!
We'll see!
Well, let's get them out here then!
Who could it be?
せーの！
Ready, set!
どうぞ！
Come on out!
ワワワワワ！クロちゃん！クロちゃんだしんよ！
Wa wa wa wa wa! It's Kuro-chan! It's Kuro-chan da shin yo!
だしんよー！
Da shin yooo!
自己紹介お願いします！
Please introduce yourself!
クロちゃんです！
I'm Kuro-chan!
ワワワワワ！
Wa wa wa wa wa!
だしんよ！
Da shin yo!
初めまして！
Nice to meet you!
チワワじゃないよ、FUWAWAだよ！
Not a Chihuahua, it's Fuwawa!
FUWAWAじゃないよ、MOCOCOだよ！
Not Fuwawa, it's Mococo!
二人合わせて...
Together we are...
FUWAMOCOです！
FUWAMOCO!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
FUWAMOCOのわちゃわちゃバースデーフェスティバルに来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to FWMC's Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival!
Happy Birthdayだしんよ！
Happy Birthday da shin yo!
FUWAMOCO!
いいしんねー！
Looking good!
ちょっとね、視聴者のラフィアンズはたくさんいると思いますけど...
Um, I think there are a lot of Ruffians watching right now, but...
...クロちゃんがどんな人なのか説明してもらえますか？
...could you explain what kind of person Kuro-chan is?
え、自分ですんのそれ？
Eh, I have to do it myself?
Introduction?
わかったしんよ。
Understood shin yo.
だってこれ海外の人も見てますもんね？
Because overseas people are watching this too, right?
海外の全員分かる自己紹介しますからね。
I'll do an intro that everyone overseas will understand.
Nice to meet you!
Chu chu chu chu...
...Tulip!
ちょっと困らないで！
Don't look so troubled!
Tulip?
No no no no no!
ちょっとまだ分からないかもしれないから...
We might not understand yet, so...
安田大サーカスっていうトリオを組んでる芸人さんで...
I'm a comedian in a trio called Yasuda Dai Circus...
あと豆柴の大群のプロデューサーもやってます...
I also work as the producer for Mameshiba no Taigun...
作詞とかもしてます...
I write lyrics too...
クロちゃんです！
I'm Kuro-chan!
じゃあ今回は英語でお願いします！
Okay, then in English this time please!
僕が！？
Me?!
自分で！？
By myself?!
そんなこと急に言われたら...
If you tell me to do that so suddenly...
It's shy...
Flower...
頑張って！
Do your best!
ファッション！
Fashion!
えーと…なんだろ、なんだろ…
Umm... what is it, what is it...
フェイマス・コメディアン！
Famous Comedian!
アンド、アイドル・プロデューサー！
And, Idol Producer!
イヤ、イヤ、クール、クール！
Yeah, yeah, cool, cool!
やってるしんよ〜！
I'm doing it-shin yo!
できる！いい！
You can do it! Nice!
クロちゃん、テレビでよく見てるけど…
Kuro-chan, we see you on TV often, but...
ちょっとフワモコのペットのペロちゃんと…
You kinda resemble FUWAMOCO's pet, Pero-chan...
えっと、ちょっと似てるところがたくさんあるね。
Umm, there are a lot of parts that look alike.
似てる！？
Look alike!?
ちょっと後ろの飾りに見てください…見えますか？
Please look at the decoration in the back... can you see it?
そう！それがペロですね！
Yes! That is Pero!
ちょっと待って！球体というか丸いところが似てるだけじゃない！？
Wait a minute! Isn't it just that we're both round spheres!?
そうじゃない？
Isn't that it?
本当？
Really?
えっと、クロちゃんと似てるところは…
Umm, the part that resembles Kuro-chan is...
嘘つきで…
Being a liar...
女の子好きで…
Liking girls...
あら！
Oh my!
やらしい！
So sleazy!
だからね、見た目で騙されないで！
So, don't be deceived by appearances!
え、クロちゃんはそんなんで大丈夫なの？言われて。
Eh, is Kuro-chan okay being told that?
いや、酷い！悲しくなってきた！
No, that's cruel! I'm getting sad!
エーン、エーン、エーン！
*Crying noises*
エンポー、ソエンフーン！
*Exaggerated crying gibberish*
ワオ〜ン！
Wao~n! (Howling)
全然、人のギャグを聞かないよね、君達は！
You two really don't listen to people's jokes at all!
できれば…
If possible...
クロちゃんはペロの友達になってくれませんか？
Would Kuro-chan please become Pero's friend?
え？フワモコの友達じゃなくて、ペロの友達なんの？
Eh? Not FUWAMOCO's friend, but Pero's friend?
そう、フワモコはクロちゃんと友達になりたくないから！
Right, because FUWAMOCO doesn't want to be Kuro-chan's friend!
おかしくない？それ！
Isn't that weird!?
いやいやいや、気持ち悪いから！
No no no, because you're creepy!
気持ち悪くない！マニアにはウケる！
I'm not creepy! I'm popular with maniacs!
いや、違う！
No, that's wrong!
気持ち悪い、やっぱり。
Creepy, as I thought.
でも、でも、モコちゃん…
But, but, Moco-chan...
ちょっとやりすぎですよ、失礼です！
That's a bit too much, it's rude!
いや、もしもペロと仲良くなって欲しいんだったら、
Well, if you really want me to get along with Pero,
フワモコちゃん、クロちゃんに可愛らしく頼んだ方がいいんじゃない？
Fuwamoco-chan, shouldn't you ask Kuro-chan cutely?
はぁ〜ん？NO！
Huuuh? NO!
NO！NO！
NO! NO!
しっかりとした否定！
A firm denial!
けど、ペロ可愛いから仲良くなってもいいとは思ってるよ。
But, Pero is cute, so I think it's okay to get along.
あ、嬉しい嬉しい！
Ah, happy happy!
可愛くないけど、なんか仲良くなってくれたら嬉しいかな。
You're not cute, but I guess I'd be happy if you got along.
感情が…感情が色々ありすぎなのよ、本当に。
There are... way too many mixed emotions, really.
まあまあ！クロちゃんって芸人さんだけど、
Now now! Kuro-chan, you are a comedian but...
アイドルになりたいんですよね、ね？
You want to become an idol, right?
そう！元々アイドルになろうと思ったのに騙されて芸人にさせられたから…
Yes! Originally I thought I'd become an idol, but I was tricked into being a comedian...
アイドルは本当に夢！ドリーム！
Being an idol is truly my dream! Dream!
なんか悲しいなぁ、可哀想。
That's kinda sad, poor thing.
でもドリームって大事ですから！大事！
But dreams are important! Important!
そう、で、まぁクロちゃんのドリームはアイドルなんだから、
So, since Kuro-chan's dream is to be an idol,
もうせっかく！一緒に歌ってくれませんか？
Why not take this chance! Won't you sing together with us?
あ！いいしんよ、いいしんよ！
Ah! That's good-shin yo, good-shin yo!
OKだしんよ！
It's OK-dashin yo!
この曲、ちょっと踊れるもんね。
This song, we can dance a bit to it.
この曲？次の曲ね？
This song? The next song right?
あの、ハードル上げないで。
Umm, don't raise the hurdle.
え、大丈夫っしょ？
Eh, it'll be fine right?
ね！アイドルのプロデュースもやってるし！
Right! You're also doing idol producing!
そうそう！
Yeah yeah!
実力見せてよ！
Show us your real skill!
見せて！
Show us!
OKだしんよ！いくしんよ、いくしんよ〜！
OK-dashin yo! Let's go-shin yo, let's go-shin yo!
オッケー！
Okay!
じゃあ、すっごく可愛い曲を一緒に歌いましょう！
Then, let's sing a super cute song together!
え、何の歌？楽しみ！
Eh, what song? Looking forward to it!
オッケー！
Okay!
じゃあ、一緒にタイトルコールしましょうね！
Then, let's do the title call together!
ね！
Okay!
せーの！『ちゅ、多様性。』
Ready! 'Chu, Tayousei.'
『多様性』やんの！？
We're doing 'Tayousei'!?
我愛你 酔いが覚めない
Wo ai ni (I love you), I won't sober up.
Oh, I need you 恋が醒めない
Oh, I need you, love won't wake up.
お生憎様の慣れ果て察して
Guess the unfortunate outcome.
無問題 破裂してみて
Mou mantai (No problem), try bursting.
Hold me tight トラウマの味
Hold me tight, the taste of trauma.
猛反対 お手お座りでハイ♡報酬
Strong objection, 'Paw', 'Sit', Yes♡ Reward.
喉の奥がチクンチクン
The back of my throat prickles.
僕はドクンドクン
My heart goes thump-thump.
鼓動で孤独消してみせてよ
Erase the loneliness with your heartbeat.
愛も恋も独裁して
Dictate both love and romance.
僕を独占して
Monopolize me.
このまま中毒になるまでチューしよう
Let's kiss until we become addicted like this.
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
熱く、とろけるくらいに溢れた気持ちが
These overflowing feelings, hot enough to melt,
たまらないでしょ
Are unbearable, right?
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
我愛你 無問題
Wo ai ni (I love you), Mou mantai (No problem).
Get get get on chu!
ポン・チー・カン 勝負はいつも
Pong, Chi, Kang, the match is always...
トンチンカン 僕に言わせりゃ
Incoherent, if you ask me.
ちんぷんかんぷんだ 最後はロンでしょ？
It's all gibberish, the end is 'Ron' right?
もう何回？ヤラれればいい
How many times? Should I be beaten?
Oh, One night 忘れられない
Oh, One night, I can't forget.
終わんない トキメキ 偏愛 予習
Never-ending heart-throbbing partiality preparation.
トキメキ変愛
Heart-throbbing strange love.
よし！
Alright!
喉の奥がチクンチクン
The back of my throat prickles.
僕はドクンドクン
My heart goes thump-thump.
心臓ごと引きずり出してみせてよ
Drag out my whole heart and show it to me.
気持ちいいね 面倒くさいけど
It feels good, even though it's troublesome.
やっぱ照れくさいけど
It's embarrassing after all, but...
死ぬまで忘れられないチューしよ
Let's share a kiss we won't forget until we die.
イカれた街はゾンビで溢れる
The crazy city is overflowing with zombies.
君は僕に恋して
You fall in love with me.
ドクメク胸に繋がるロープを引きなよ
Pull the rope connected to my throbbing chest.
Bet bet bet on... Bet on chu!
本気で狂えちゃうくらいの鬱々しさが
The gloominess that could seriously drive me crazy...
美しいでしょ
Is beautiful, isn't it?
Get get get on... Get on chu!
せーの！
One, two!
ポン・チー・カン 終わんない
Pon-Chi-Kan, it never ends.
Get get get on chu!
我愛你 無問題
I love you, no problem.
Get get get on chu!
わー！やったー！
Wow! We did it!
うまく行ったしんよー！
It went well, shin!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
よかった！
That was great!
頑張ったね、クロちゃん！
You worked hard, Kuro-chan!
楽しかった、ありがとう！
That was fun, thank you!
サンキュー！
Thank you!
えっと... さよならする前に...
Um... before we say goodbye...
え、なに？
Eh, what?
一個お願いしてもいいですか？
Can I ask for one favor?
一個だけだしんよ
Just one thing, shin.
一個だけじゃあ...
Just one thing, then...
えっと... FUWAMOCOは魔界の番犬で...
Um... FUWAMOCO are Demon Guard Dogs...
バウバウをよく言ってるんですけど
and we often say 'Bau Bau'...
クロちゃん、カメラに向かって
Kuro-chan, facing the camera...
FUWAMOCOのように可愛い...
Just like FUWAMOCO, a cute...
バウバウをしてもらえますか？
...'Bau Bau', could you do it?
えー！できるかなー！
Ehh! I wonder if I can!
いくしんよ！
Here I go, shin!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
それがベスト？
Is that your best?
もう一回！
One more time!
もっとやって！
Do it more!
はいはい！うーん...
Okay, okay! Hmmm...
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
可愛いかな？
Is it cute?
実はもう一個やりたいことがあるんですけど
Actually, there is one more thing I want to do.
もう何？
What is it now?
先ほどやりましたけど
We did it earlier, but...
FUWAMOCOはいつもやってる自己紹介があって
FUWAMOCO has a self-introduction we always do.
できれば三人で一緒にやりたいです！
If possible, I want to do it with all three of us!
あ、あれ可愛かったから
Ah, that was cute so...
やりたい、クロちゃんも！
I want to do it too, Kuro-chan does!
じゃあ行きますよー！
Then here we go!
オッケー！
Okay!
ふわふわじゃないよ
Not fluffy fluffy (Fuwafuwa)...
フワワだよ！
It's Fuwawa!
わわわわー！
Wa wa wa wa!
フワワじゃないよ！
Not Fuwawa!
クロちゃんだよ！
It's Kuro-chan!
ええ！？
Ehh!?
クロちゃんじゃないよ！
Not Kuro-chan!
モココだよ！
It's Mococo!
三人に合わせて！
Align with the three of us!
合わせて！
Align it!
いやいやいや！
No no no no!
怒んないで！どうしたの？
Don't get mad! What's wrong?
出てけクロちゃん！
Get out, Kuro-chan!
出てかないから！
I'm not leaving!
なんなのそれ！
What is that!
もう嘘とかつくのやめようね
Let's stop telling lies already.
やらないと！
I have to do it!
モココパーンチしちゃうよ！
I'm gonna Mococo Punch you!
痛ーい！
Ouuuch!
救急車一台！
One ambulance!
いらないよ！
We don't need it!
もう嘘！
Another lie!
いらないって何それ！
What do you mean we don't need it!
プンプン！
Hmph hmph! (Angry SFX)
なんてプンプン怒んのちょっと！
Why are you getting so angry!
落ち着いて、落ち着いて！
Calm down, calm down!
なんで？
Why?
大丈夫、モコちゃん大丈夫！
It's okay, Moco-chan, it's okay!
クロちゃんはこれからも...
Kuro-chan, from now on...
みんなをいっぱい笑顔にして
...make everyone smile a lot...
素敵なアイドルになってくださいね！
...and please become a wonderful idol!
任せしんよ！
Leave it to me, shin!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
じゃあモコちゃん
Then Moco-chan...
はーい
Yes?
最後にクロちゃんにハイタッチしてお別れしようね
Let's high-five Kuro-chan and say goodbye.
おっけー！
Okay!
仲直り仲直り、いい？
Reconciliation, reconciliation, okay?
仲直りね！
Reconciliation, right!
いくしんよ！
Here I go, shin!
ハイタッチ！ハイタッチ！
High five! High five!
ほらほらほらほら！
Come on, come on, come on!
やってみて！やってみて！
Try it! Try it!
ほらやってやって！
Come on, do it, do it!
仲直り仲直り！
Reconciliation, reconciliation!
うわーっ！
Waaah!
あーちょっと！
Ah, hey!
へへーん！
Heheee!
ひどくない？
Isn't that mean?
もうちょっと！
Geez!
なんなの？
What is it?
けど！
But!
FUWAMOCOちゃん、本当にお誕生日おめでとうございます！
FUWAMOCO-chan, really, Happy Birthday!
わー！ありがとう！
Wow! Thank you!
おめでただしんよ！
Happy Birthday, shin!
キュンからのバッキュン！
From Kyun to Bakkyun!
おめでとう、ハート！
Congratulations, heart!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
Let's stay going!
Let's keep going!
Fireworks!
Look at the beautiful fireworks! Yeah!
Tamaya~!
Kagiya~!
Bau Bau!
Wow!
That was so fun!
Things kind of got really crazy there...
I'm not too sure what happened...
なんか色々すごすぎて分からなくなってきたかも
It was all so amazing, I might be getting confused.
But we still have one more thing!
One more very exciting thing to share with you all!
まだまだ楽しみがあるよ！
There's still more fun to come!
Maybe... Ruffians... can you guess what it is?
何かな？何かな？
What is it? What is it?
Well... Fuwamoco...
On our first anniversary...
Going to be fun!
And then for our second anniversary...
we were able to release "Lifetime Showtime"!
Our original song that's grown with us along this journey.
A very special song.
And you know, for Fuwawa and Mococo, singing and dancing is something that means so much to us.
And Ruffians...
might have heard that you'd like to hear more from us too.
Right?
What do you think?
Well...
The announcement is...
Drumroll!
Dan!
Bam!
A new original song!
And this song is extra special.
It's written by none other than the legendary rock idol song composer...
Matsukuma Kenta-san!
Who works with many famous idol groups that we love.
Also written music for the idol group that Kuro-chan produces, Mameshiba no Taigun-san!
But Ruffians, you might be a little bit surprised, okay?
So get ready.
Ruffians...
With this song...
we'd like to express our rawest feelings as demon dogs.
Demon's Residence
「相棒、どこへ行こうか」
"Partner, where shall we go?"
ネオンの脇を抜け
Slip past the neon lights.
バブルガムがはじけたら let's go
When the bubblegum pops, let's go.
最低な夜を潜って
Diving under the worst kind of night,
僕らは群れをなす
We form a pack.
「あの頃よりもマシだね」 my way
"It's better than back then," my way.
「不完全なんです」
"I am imperfect."
首輪をつけた
Wearing a collar,
良い子なんかじゃもうイヤ Ah!!
I don't wanna be a "good girl" anymore, Ah!!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
噛みついていけ
Bite into it.
この街は檻のようで
This city is like a cage.
気分はどうだい
How does it feel?
泣いているのかい
Are you crying?
鎖をちぎって叫んでいたいんだ
I want to tear off these chains and scream.
stray dogs
遥か彼方へと飛ぶ鳥を
The birds flying far away into the distance,
見上げるだけかい
Are you just going to look up at them?
それでいいのかい
Is that enough for you?
燃えるなら ほら青く
If you're gonna burn, then burn blue.
「説教なんかいらない」
"I don't need any lectures."
スプレー缶振って
Shake the spray can.
イタズラ書きで彩る runway
Color the runway with graffiti.
愛情なんか coin toss
Love is just a coin toss.
誰にbetするのか
Who are you gonna bet on?
不確定要素ばかりね lonely
It's all just uncertain factors, lonely.
二人で
The two of us,
ひとつと決めた
decided to be one.
あの日を忘れない Ah!!
I won't forget that day, Ah!!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
満天の空
The sky full of stars,
あの星がひどく不快で
that star is terribly unpleasant.
勝利はどうだい
How is victory?
味がするのかい
Does it have a taste?
鎖を噛んで唸っていたんだ
Biting the chains, I was growling.
stray dogs
僕ら宇宙さえも撃ち落として
We shoot down even the cosmos.
見下ろす奈落
The abyss looking down,
ビルは輝く
The buildings shine.
LOL Now I am free!
孤独を分け合い
We shared our loneliness,
食べた
and devoured it.
あの日を忘れない
I won't forget that day.
鳴呼
Ah...
夜を睨んだ stray dogs そうだ
Stray dogs glaring at the night, that's right.
怪物は世界のほうさ
The world is the real monster.
抜け出せるのかい
Can you escape?
足は動くかい
Do your legs move?
走るなら今
If you're gonna run, do it now.
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
stray dogs 僕ら
stray dogs, we are...
この街を駆けて行け
Run through this city.
地獄の果てに
At the end of hell,
何が見えるかい
what will we see?
鎖をちぎって叫んでいたいんだ
I want to tear off these chains and scream.
stray dogs 僕ら
stray dogs, we are...
この街は檻のようで
This city is like a cage.
君ならどうだい
How about you?
共にかけるかい
Will you run with us?
夜明けが合図だ
Dawn is the signal,
行こう
let's go.
アンコール! アンコール!
Encore! Encore!
Bau bau!
Thank you for always being here for us, Ruffians!
Please listen to... side by side!
Finally we made it through
but not without some tears
With the help of friends so true
we faced all of our feelings
Now we're here to celebrate
all that we have done
I can feel it's more than just a game of fate
'cause our stories have just begun
Hand in hand we're not waiting on tomorrow
From now on it's the heart that we will follow
We'll move on past the heartbreak and the sorrow if you
Stay by my side
Dancing harmonies feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Even though there's been rough times
where nobody wanted us
We kept going!
And we kept dreaming!
Now we're here
we're not alone anymore!
So be here together
with a smile to protect!
Come on, let's go!
Dancing harmonies feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Nya, nya nya nya...
Bau bau!
Thank you for the encore Ruffians!
That was side by side!
We really sang side by side for you for the first time live today!
初披露できてとっても嬉しい！
I'm so happy we could perform it for the first time!
Side by side is a song made by Aiobahn-san...
but also featuring FUWAMOCO!
You know, we know it's a song that you love a lot...
but we love it too because...
it's very special to us since it's the ending theme...
for a visual novel that we care about!
Nekopara!
And with this song...
our dream of singing the opening or ending theme for a visual novel came true!
そう、この曲でフワモコの夢...
Yes, with this song, FUWAMOCO's dream...
美少女ゲームの主題歌を歌うことが叶いました！
of singing a bishoujo game theme song came true!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
And thank you so much for joining us for a special day again this year!
It's been a dream, Ruffians!
And you know...
it's all because of you that we're able to be here...
and do all the amazing things that we do, so...
Thank you!
Ah... Right...
But... like, above all... it's a very special one.
You know, FuwaMoco...
...as Demon Guard Dogs...
...we're here to protect your smile, right?
We'll continue to do that!
Protect your smile!
Yeah! Do our all as idols!
And satisfy our fluffy and fuzzy souls too!
Yeah!
We'll continue to be here for thousands and thousands of Demon Dog years!
And we'll remember that, you know... every day isn't given.
We don't take anything for granted.
And you know, when you're down,
we hope that you'll remember that we're always here cheering you on, okay?
We'll cheer you on always!
So please listen closely to the lyrics of our last song for today.
明日も明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように ずっと
I hope you are smiling, forever.
lala...
Thank you so much Ruffians for spending our birthday with us today!
Please think of this song whenever things are rough,
and know that we'll be here!
This last song is for you!
Wishful Garnet!
過去を振り返ると思い出す
When I look back at the past, I remember
茜色の空
The madder red sky,
溢れてく光
and the overflowing light.
この瞳に映し出されたあの日は
That day reflected in these eyes,
美しく揺れる
shimmers beautifully.
What do you think?
赤く滲んだ空に
To the red-stained sky,
願いました
I made a wish.
どうかこの願い
Please, let this wish...
届けてください
...be delivered.
明日も明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope you are smiling.
離れ離れになっても
Even if we are far apart,
前を向けますように
I hope you can look forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you,
わたしが壊してあげる
I will break them for you.
もう負けないで
Don't lose anymore,
進むことを
the will to move forward.
いつでもそばにいるから
Because I'm always by your side.
落ち込んだり自信を無くした時だって
Even when you're down or lose confidence,
目の前にいてくれる
you are right there in front of me.
あなたの笑顔に何度となく救われた
I've been saved by your smile countless times.
だから So I love you 挫けそうになったら
That's why, so I love you. If you feel like giving up,
手を伸ばして まだ知らない明日
Reach out your hand, to the tomorrow we don't know yet.
一緒に見つけよう
Let's find it together.
明日も
Tomorrow,
明後日も あなたを照らしていたい
and the day after too, I want to keep shining on you.
泣きそうになった時は
When you feel like crying,
こっち向いてほしい
I want you to look this way.
世界でひとりぼっち
All alone in the world...
そんな風に思わないで
don't think like that.
愛してくれる人はきっと
The people who love you are surely,
いつもあなたを想ってる
always thinking of you.
Wishful Garnet
Lalalala...
願いました どうかこの願い
I made a wish. Please, let this wish...
届けてください
...be delivered.
明日も明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope you are smiling.
離れ離れになっても
Even if we are far apart,
前を向けますように
I hope you can look forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you,
わたしが壊してあげる
I will break them for you.
もう負けないで 進むことを
Don't lose the will to move forward anymore.
輝く空へ
To the shining sky.
明日も
Tomorrow,
明後日も あなたが笑ってますように
and the day after too, I hope you are smiling.
前を向けますように
May you be able to look forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you...
わたしが壊してあげる
I will break them for you.
もう負けないで進むこと
Don't give up, keep moving forward.
いつでもそばに
Always by your side.
あなたのそばに
Right by your side.
わたしはいつもいるから
Because I'm always here with you.
La la la la la...
Oh yeah...
Yeah yeah...
La ha...
BAU BAU!
Thank you so much for viewing!
We'll see you soon at our encore live in membership!
Okay?
BAU BAU!
SEE YOU AT OUR ENCORE LIVE IN MEMBERSHIP!
メン限アンコールライブで待ってるよー!
We'll be waiting for you at the members-only encore live!